These people are just happier than you,
America. If you're in America watching
this, I'm here to tell you something.
Water is colorless, odorless, and
tasteless. Rain does not have a smell
here. Do you want to know what Costa
Rica is about? You learn this by Asmos.
If you bring your ass, your brain will
follow.
>> What is life like here, and how does it
compare to the States?
>> There's food growing in the ground
everywhere. There's no military here.
There's no cameras on the street
corners. There's people hurting cows in
the road. This whole family's riding on
one dirt bike with the mom in the front
and the oldest kid in the back and the
two [music] middle ones bunched together
in a fourpack. My first reaction was
like, "Oh my god, look at how Wait a
minute. Them kids are having the time of
their life. Love to ride a motorcycle at
age five." Way better him. There's no
engine noise. I've never seen a
chemtrail unless I call somebody. Nobody
ever comes here. The police don't mess
with me one bit. They're actually kind
of nice. I met one and he brought me
gifts. You have to come here. I can't
tell you the video. I can sit here and
talk in front of this camera [music] for
10 hours and describe all of these
wonderful experiences for you, but it'
be like telling you what the air smells
like here. Rain does not have a smell
here. [music] You cannot smell that
ozone drop. It has no smell. You know
why? Water is colorless, odorless, and
tasteless. Dirty, polluted water falling
from the sky and passing through dirty,
polluted air will stank. You would never
know that unless you just showed the
[__] up here. Jesus said, "If you seek,
you will find. If you knock, it will be
open to you." He didn't say, [music]
"Drop a text, dog. Comment on
Instagram." He didn't say, "Look." He
said, "Seek." Yeah, you have to do a
little seeking, man. You learn this by
ask Moses. If you bring your ass, your
brain will follow and you will
understand everything I'm trying to
configurify for you, [__] I do
not think it's braining in there right
now. Not no son. No s. You don't need an
air conditioner. There's no animals in
the river that don't harm you. There's
no crocodiles. you know, Kiman's this
far up that have respect for nature or
they will come fee and find your ass.
And that's what government should do.
The central theme of their their
government is making it harder to [__]
up nature. They're here protecting
nature. Don't [__] with a tree, an
animal, or a river. You can't transport
a tree in the road without a permit.
Half of this country is designated not
to ever be touched by man. And it's
different than our national parks that
have a visitor center and paved roads
all through it. took the wolves out of
Yellowstone and then added them back.
Like everything else in America,
synthetic as hell, but presented as
real. Candy here has a warning label on
the front. There's barely any to choose
from. The water I drink is
just runs out of the top of the mountain
and then it runs through tanks. Sediment
collects and the water runs out the top.
[music]
That's the water I drink every day.
Flows out of the top of the mountain.
I've lost 10 lbs since I've been here.
Before that, I was a competitive ultr
runner. I've won 40 and 50 mile foot
races, 26 milei races. I want to be like
the Tikos cuz they're old men aren't
old. They make dig jokes and they work
all day and they have energy. They're
vivacious and they're happy. These
people are just happier than you,
America. I don't want all of you coming
here and [__] this place up. That's
not what I said. I said these people are
happier than you and it's because they
live a better, simpler life than you.
I'm going to back rest for a minute
before I cuss out all the [__] world.
Get me basing powder, please.